[unsettling foreboding music]
- It appears that village is
indeed amassing military might
and planning something
most dreadful.
- It may be that they're
convincing Flowrem
to stay there just so that
they can use her
as a hostage if they need to.
- We should begin gathering
our troops at once...
Princess!
I understand.
We must defeat that village
and we have to save Flowrem.
["Flower Ring" by Shino Shimoji
and Aya Suzaki plays]
[waves lapping]
[minimal pensive music]
[magic humming]
- I'm sorry to bother you
while you're looking busy.
- I'm not just looking busy,
I am busy.
I have been put in charge of the
village's accounting practices.
Putting that aside, what brings
you here so late, Father?
- The thing is, our princess
is gathering troops
and preparing to go on
a military campaign.
[Flowrem gasping]
- [Flowrem] Our princess
is doing what?
Why would she do
something so absurd?
- While you have been away
from the kingdom,
some have taken the chance to
fill her head with half-truths.
- And by some, you mean.
- The second daughter
of the Gritch family,
the fourth daughter
of the Bugal family,
and the second daughter
of the Mamonrose family.
- Aren't those the trio of
politically powerful idiots?
So where exactly are they
planning to attack?
- This very village.
- Huh?
What in the world would
give them such a dumb idea?
I've given them
plenty of reports.
They should know how powerful
this village is.
- I think the reports
were so ridiculous
that they started
to seem unreal.
I tried to have the demon lord
put a stop to this rampage.
But he's far too soft
on his daughter.
- Then do you think it's best
if I convince them to stop?
- They would be
expecting you to do that.
It would cause them to
view you as an enemy
of the Demonic Kingdom.
- Then what should I do, Father?
- I just need you to stop their
invasion before it starts.
- [Flowrem] When are
they mobilizing?
- Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?
- Their forces number 300 men.
I was thinking that maybe if
someone from this village
routed their forces,
they'd give up and go home.
- Sure, but if we're careless
about which villagers
find out about this,
it will likely cause
a violent destruction
of the Demonic Kingdom.
- [Beezel] That would
be a problem.
- Hmm, so then, I just need to
show them the difference
in military might without
mobilizing the village's forces.
[people shouting indistinctly]
[explosive blasting]
[wood breaking]
[people yelling]
- We beg of you,
please, spare our lives!
- [Soldier] Have mercy!
- Hmm?
[people gasping]
Are we done already?
- [Soldiers] Yes.
- They're going to give us
ten boxes of apples
just for this?
Do you think maybe we should
punish them just a little more?
- Uh, so who are these girls
standing here frozen solid?
- They're from
the Demonic Kingdom,
and they'd like to
move here.
They've had a change of heart
and are ready to work
themselves to death.
- [Girls] Huh?
- I mean, they're ready to work
like their lives depend on it.
- Um, okay.
But even so.
They kind of seem like
they've given up.
Almost like they've accepted
that their lives are over,
or something.
- They'll be fine.
They're all
acquaintances of mine.
So for the time being,
I plan to have them
working for me.
In the event they harm
the village in any way,
please don't hesitate
to dispose of them.
I won't mind.
- That sounded scary.
Great, now that
that's out of the way,
who's that other girl
over there?
- She's here to observe.
I'd like to show her how things
work here in the village.
- My... my name is Yuri.
- Apparently, she was
very worried
about my living conditions
here in our village and
wanted to see what it's like.
- You don't need to
give her special treatment.
Please put her to work
knowing she'll be gone soon.
- How does she expect me
to do that?
Great, why don't you
show them around.
- Thank you,
just leave it to me.
Listen up.
If you all put in some
honest work here,
your transgressions against
the village will be forgiven.
That said, in the interest
of keeping this incident
a secret from the rest
of the villagers,
it would be wise not to
divulge your identities.
In other words, Princess.
- Yes, Flowrem?
- You won't get
special treatment.
As long as you're here,
in this village,
you'll just be plain old Yuri.
- That won't be a problem.
[Yuri giggling]
It's been a long time since
I've been called by my name.
- Now then, let's get started
with our tour of the village.
[Flowrem sighing]
[mild carefree music]
- So these fruit are
turned into alcohol?
These plants grow
from inside the water?
[mechanisms warbling]
This contraption
moves not with magic,
but it's powered by
water moving over it?
- [Beastboys] Hello.
- Are you one of the new girls?
- So, Fluffy, look at you.
- Hey, that tickles.
- These are apples, right?
I had no idea they
grew on trees like this.
[girls ahhing]
- Oh hey, do we have
some visitors?
- I have never gotten
to eat apples
except for when attending
parties at the castle.
- I ate them every day at home,
never missed a day.
- At my house, we used to
have the merchants
search for them and buy them up
when in short supply.
- [Roaju] So that's
where they went.
- Are those girls that are
with you nobles or something?
- Yeah, yeah,
something like that.
- If we can take over
this village.
- It'll be the biggest
money-maker for our kingdom.
- [Flowrem] Dispose.
- Never mind, forget it,
it's nothing.
[girls giggling]
- Hello there,
I'm Lastismoon of the dragons.
Please call me Lasty.
- Nice to meet you, Lasty.
She's awfully adorable
for a fierce dragon.
- I know we were
forced to stay out here
but it's gross that
nobles are living
in the middle of
nowhere like this.
- We'll be the laughing stock of
the country when we're back.
- Let's wait for a chance
and escape.
[girls agreeing]
[girls gasping]
[wolves growling]
[girls screaming]
[rooster crowing]
[girls whimpering]
[air whooshing]
[girls screaming]
[girls whimpering]
- [Flowrem] Have you
learned your lesson?
- [Girls] We have.
- We promise you.
- [Klakkase] We'll work like
our lives depend on it.
- [Rosalind] Just please
don't dispose of us.
- Looks like they're
working really hard.
- They're actually a big help.
Now I can split up the mountain
of office work I had to do.
I'll be happy if I can
keep them working like this
as part of the town hall.
[wolf panting]
[wolf cooing]
[Flowrem giggling]
[warm carefree music]
- That's an inferno wolf
your playing with, isn't it?
Is it all right for you to
be petting it like that?
- Yeah.
Even though a single
inferno wolf
is said to be dangerous enough
to cause serious damage
and harm to any city it enters,
they're really cute
when they're like this.
- [Yuri] I'm supposed
to throw this?
- [Flowrem] Yeah, they love it.
- Let's see.
Go!
[wolf barking]
[wolves barking]
I could get use to this.
- Eventually.
- This village has been nothing
but wonderful surprises.
I can't believe a world
like this exists
outside of the Kingdom.
- I'm pretty sure this is
a very rare exception.
- No, I was just very ignorant
of the outside world.
I tried to bring
war and conflict
to such a wonderfully peaceful
and tranquil village.
- Anyone who intends to do harm
will find themselves on
the receiving end
of a dragon's fire breath.
- And indeed they should.
To be honest,
I thought the intel about
dragons living in this village
was a lie meant to deceive
the Demonic Kingdom.
- I warned everyone
on the council
not to get involved
with this village.
The demon lord should've
warned you against it as well.
So why did you do it?
- Honestly, it's your fault.
[Flowrem gasping]
Flowrem, you vanished from the
Demonic Kingdom without warning!
I heard that you had
become a hostage.
I was deeply worried
about you.
- I'm honored, Prin-
- My name is Yuri!
Stop acting subserviant,
we've been friends
since childhood!
You stopped asking me for help,
and then before I knew it,
everything was
princess this and
princess that.
Like I was a stranger.
- I'm sorry, Yuri.
I'll keep you in the loop
from now on.
- I know, Flowrem.
- Yeah.
Now, let's head back.
It's almost time
for us to eat.
- Okay.
[girls sighing]
- This office work
is really hard
but the food here is great.
- We don't have to worry about
any stressful politics.
We can just relax here.
- The baths really heal my soul.
[girls giggling]
- I was worried that they might
have trouble adjusting.
- Seems they've already
fully adapted.
- Are these three
the new girls?
- Yeah. Huh?
You've been at that height
all day, haven't you?
- Yeah, my transformation magic
hasn't really been
working lately.
Oh well, I'm sure
it'll get better.
- I see then.
- [Hiraku] Farming Life...
- [Girls] In another...
- [Hiraku] World.
[stream babbling]
- Right, I know.
[both gasping]
- Ah.
- Huh?
- [Beastboys] It's Big Sis!
- If you don't mind,
I would like to help out
with the farm work as well.
- She's going to do
manual labor?
- But that's work for commoners.
- Please stop this, Princess.
- [Beastboys] Princess?
- Pardon?
Wasn't that a secret?
- [Girls] Forget we said that.
- Disposal.
[girls whimpering]
- Now then, I want you all
to join me and help out.
- Huh? But we.
- Our specialty is office work
not hard manual labor.
- Don't worry,
we'll show you how.
- [Girls] Ugh.
[peaceful cheerful music]
- I learned a lot from you all
during my time
here in this village.
I'm grateful to you all.
- [Beastboy]
You're leaving already?
- I'm sorry. I promise to
come visit you often.
- Uh.
- Um, here.
- [Yuri] Oh my.
- [Sena] They're made
from the wheat
that we harvested together.
- Thank you all so very much.
Flowrem.
Don't forget to come visit.
- Of course.
- [Yuri] Thank you too
for your hospitality, mayor.
- Sure, travel safe.
- Oh, by the way,
are you all not
coming home with me?
[bell dinging]
- There are still
so many great things
left for us to learn
within this village.
- And there's still a ton
of work left to do.
- We haven't repayed
everyone's kindness.
- Therefore, we must stay.
- [Yuri] Could you please stop
eating while you're talking.
- We should leave now.
- Right.
Everyone, I'll see you again.
[magic warbling]
- Looks like she
enjoyed her time here.
- Indeed.
- [Galgardo] Hey, Beezel.
- [Beezel] Yes.
- It's about Yuri, ever since
she returned to the castle,
she's seems a bit
different somehow.
- Yes.
- It's like she's grown
dignified all of a sudden.
She looks so busy now.
Even if I try to have
a conversation,
she doesn't make the time.
- It seems that
the princess will begin
to take an interest in politics
and diplomacy pretty soon.
Daughters tend to
grow into adults
before their parents
realize it.
- An adult?
Don't tell me...
she's met a man!
[menacing music]
Who is he?
I, the great
demon lord Galgardo
will tear him apart with
my bare hands myself.
- That possessive attitude
is going to make her
hate you one day.
- She'll hate me?
[Galgardo growling]
- More importantly,
it's time for a meeting.
Let's go and show her what
a cool father you can be.
- Okay, I get it.
Leave it to me.
- [Hiraku] A short while
after Yuri left,
we began our pre-winter
crop harvest
and this was the result.
When did all of this happen?
- [Tia] We harvested so much,
this is what we couldn't
fit into storage.
- I'm glad we had
a good harvest.
- But this is more
than we thought.
- In that case, would it
be all right with you
if I sent some of it
to my father?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Oh then, can we send
some to mine?
- That's fine by me, but who
are your parents anyway?
- [Lastismoon]
From my perspective,
they're Granddad and Grandmom.
- My father lives in
the northern continent
while my mother
lives in the south,
so I'm afraid it's going to be
a bit out of the way.
- There are dragons
north and south?
If that's true then you
must be referring to
the Emperor Dragon Doze,
and the the Hurricane
Dragon Raimaylen
- You're exaggerating!
Is that really
what you call them?
- I never knew the dragons
were all connected like this.
- Those are some
pretty intense names.
First, Lasty
stopped by Dryme's
and dropped off the food
we were sharing.
Then she continued
to Shashato City
to drop off their
share of crops.
Apparently, Michael asked her
to exterminate a monster
that had been attacking
the trade vessels.
- Sure thing.
You're mine!
[explosive blasting]
Guess what? I got to
take some meat home
as thanks for
killing that thing.
This is definitely
that chanco stuff
you were talking about, mayor.
That means we're having
chanco hotpot tonight.
- Uh, yeah.
Meanwhile, Hakuren headed north.
On her way back,
she found some people
that wanted to
move to our village.
- I'm Ya, the leader of
this group.
- Are you dark elves?
- What?
No, that's not what we are,
we're known as mountain elves.
- Uh, sorry, my mistake.
Please forget about it.
- They can all use fire,
and they're also meat eaters,
like my elven clan.
- So I see.
- Normally, all of us
live up in the mountains,
but as of late, it's become
harder for us to find food.
- They seemed like they were
having some trouble...
so I thought it might be
easier if they lived here.
- I see.
Hmm...
What should we do?
- I do understand
that no one has the leeway
to help strangers.
If we're causing you trouble,
we'll leave right away.
- No, that's not what I meant.
- Huh?
- I was trying to
think of a plan.
We need to figure out
where you'll sleep...
until we can
build you a house.
I was thinking on who
I'll need to talk to first.
- So then?
- Yeah.
If you're okay with
living here with us.
[Ya shrieking]
- Thank you so much!
And don't worry, we're fine
sleeping on the ground here.
- [Hiraku] No,
we can't have that.
And so, the group of
mountain elves
became residents
of our village.
- At the very least,
we'll go catch food on our own.
We're excellent hunters.
[lively cheerful music]
[Ya yelling]
[Ya screaming]
Uh, I'm terribly sorry
we couldn't be of more use.
- Are you okay?
- [Ya] Is there something
wrong with this forest?
- You think so, too?
Don't hurt yourselves
if its too much.
- That's very
thoughtful of you, mayor.
What's that you're working on?
- Uh.
I was hoping we could
make some pottery here.
- Interesting.
- And now, we bake it
after it's all dry.
- Oh.
[deflated warbling]
What happened to it?
- I guess the soil here
just won't work.
We'll have to go look around
for clay somewhere.
- Please, mayor, would you allow
me the honor of finding that?
We come from the mountains,
and as such,
we understand the earth and
what all lies within it.
- I see.
Isn't it dangerous to
search the area?
- As long as I don't have to
fight, I should be all right.
I'm confident in
my ability to flee.
- Just promise me
you'll be careful.
Wow!
This is great, it's perfect!
- [Ya] I did my best.
- [Hiraku] I wonder if
we can make cups,
and plates, and stuff.
- Of course!
Just leave it to me.
[air whipping]
- [Hiraku] They found
another dungeon?
- Yes, it's a different one
than where the lamia live.
Ya was able to find the entrance
to the dungeon up north
near the mountains.
I'd like your permission
to send a survey party.
- What if it's dangerous?
- That's one reason we need to
survey the area and learn more.
- I see then.
Well, just don't do
anything too drastic.
- All right, we're
gonna head out now.
- While the survey team was
off investigating the dungeon,
the men's bathhouse
was finally finished.
[Hiraku exhaling]
The dwarves and
the lizardmen can use it,
and so can Dryme
when he visits.
So I definitely didn't build
this just so I could have it.
Yep.
[Beastboys laughing]
[water splashing]
Well, I don't mind
how lively it is here.
Remember, you need to
make sure to wash yourselves
before getting in here.
- [Beastboys] Okay.
[startling music]
- Just what exactly do you three
think you're doing out here?
- We... thought this was
the women's bathhouse.
- I won't get mad, so just
tell me the truth, okay?
- [Rosalind] You're about to get
really mad at us, aren't you?
- Well, um, we were
hoping that maybe
we could wash the
mayor's back for him?
- We thought it could be a good
chance to get closer to him.
- Listen up.
We're the absolute
lowest-ranking members
in this village.
- What did I say? Bad idea.
- I tried to stop this.
- Huh, what, seriously?
- You know what'll happen
if you try that again.
- [Roaju] Please, don't let
them dispose of us.
- [Flowrem] Last warning.
- Huh?
Before long, the dungeon
survey party had returned.
You're all here.
What is it then?
- We should send an
extermination party
to the dungeon up north.
- Something there a problem?
- We confirmed the presence
of a blood viper inside.
[unsettling music]
- Oh, that was the thing
fighting the bear.
- We absolutely
must have its meat.
The survival of our clan depends
on us getting ahold of it.
- Is it really that important?
- Yes, blood viper meat is said
to be extremely valuable.
Eating it fills you
with vitality,
improves one's
husband-wife relations,
and is said to even
bless you with children.
[infant crying]
[Ya gasping]
- [Hiraku] Well,
it's almost winter.
Let's talk it over
with the village
before we set out to hunt it.
[mellow music]
And so, autumn faded away
as winter began to approach.
Then one day...
[door creaking]
- Huh?
I never thought I'd see
you of all people bedridden.
What a strange sight
for one to witness.
- Are you okay?
I heard you weren't
feeling well.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I might have just caught a cold.
- [Tia] Isn't mixing up
different kinds
of medicines your specialty?
- [Lu] I've never tried making a
medicine for myself before this.
[Hiraku grunting]
Don't look at me like that.
It's just a bit of nausea
and a slight fever is all.
I'm sure I'll be fine if I rest
for a little while.
- I hope that's all it is.
- This might be a long shot,
but have you found yourself
craving sour foods?
- Uh, now that you mention it,
I don't really have an appetite
but I'm still able to eat
tomatoes and fruits.
- [Tia and Sena] Mm...
- Um, there was someone
in Howling Village
who said the same thing.
- Huh?
- Lulucy, have you
really not figured out
what's happening to you?
- No, what is it?
- That person?
What happened to them?
- Well, um...
We congratulated them
on the baby.
- Hmm...
- [Hiraku and Lu] What?!
["Feel the winds"
by Yui Hizuki plays]
[rustic music playing]